ALIMI YEMI AREMU

ADDRESS: 1, Adeoye Street, Jegede Area, Akanran Road, Ibadan, Oyo State. PHONE NUMBER: 08138103982

EMAIL: yemialimi@gmail.com

PERSONAL DETAILS

■ Sex: Male

■ Date of birth: 13th March, 1994

Marital Status: Single
Place of Birth: Ibadan
Local Govt. Area: Ona-Ara
State of birth: Oyo State
Nationality: Nigeria

OBJECTIVE

To join a reputable organization using my experience and competence in identifying, creating and exploring opportunities in the environment. And also to provide strategic skills, ideas and solution that will facilitate the accomplishment of the organization's goals and objectives.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND WITH DATES

Federal Polytechnic Offa, Kwara State	2015-2017
Federal Polytechnic Offa, Kwara State	2011-2014
Moslem Senior Grammer School II, Odinjo Ibadan.	2007-2010
Elekuro High School III, Ogbere Tioya Ibadan, Nigeria	2004-2007
Jesus The Rock Institute, Jegede Akanran Road Ibadan	1998-2004

QUALIFICATIONS WITH DATES

Higher National Diploma Business Admin and Management (UPPER CREDIT)	2017
National Diploma Business Admin and Management (DISTINCTION)	2014
Senior Secondary School Certificate	2010
Primary School Leaving Certificate	2004

PERSONAL SKILLS

Ability to use computer applications such as Microsoft Office Packages (Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint and Access), Corel Draw and Adobe PageMaker.

Excellent and good communication skill.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Employer: M.K. Telecommunication, Jegede area, Akanran Road, Ibadan.

Period: 2016 - 2021 Designation: Sales Rep.

Employer: National Youth Service Corp.

Period: 2017 - 2018. Designation: Teaching

HOBBIES

Surfing the internet, traveling, watching movies and exploring good ideas

REFERENCES

Available on request.